[Music]
Oh
First of all, why is our helmet
important? Let's cut it short. We shouldn't lose a life if
it happens in an accident. Life loss is not acceptable. Is
it the driver's error or the accident's
error? We
say where all the errors are. We do
our research and
punish people for no use. Because of who we
punish, it is because there is no use. That's why the
insurance company and the court get
involved in this. You come up with
some scheme,
make some drop. But life should not be lost. You can increase the
penalty section extra for that.
Or you can increase the awareness.
But no life should be lost for a trivial reason. Every year, we
take our statistics and look at
this.  When
comparing this year with last year,
we have reduced the number of deaths by one fifth in Chennai City Police in 2023 compared to 2022.
Now, it has come down to 24 in 2023 compared to 2022, which is much lower.
But what we are facing is that the number of vehicles in
2023 is higher than the number in 2022, and
now in
2024, there are still more vehicles than in 2022,
but the infrastructure we have is
the same. So, if we strike
this balance and drive without accidents, all of us, the
road users,
can reduce these accidents. You must have seen in this audio the effort taken by
this
administration and this insurance company to save these lives.
We don't need anyone's
advice.  Similarly, we have created
this Terms
and Conditions Road Safety Helmet
Awareness so that we do not disturb anyone's life unnecessarily. If you follow this daily, we will
reduce the number of lives lost by this queja. It is unfair. No life will go
careless.
So, take this opportunity and take a pledge not to drive without a helmet. If you follow it daily, you can avoid unnecessary life loss. We can create a healthy society. So,
thank you very much to all the deacons who have been involved in this. The police have given us this opportunity.